<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Cottage Painter</title><link>https://cottagepainter.github.io/</link><description>Recent content on Cottage Painter</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2019 15:08:48 -0400</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://cottagepainter.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Glossary</title><link>https://cottagepainter.github.io/resources/glossary/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2019 15:08:48 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://cottagepainter.github.io/resources/glossary/</guid><description>Caulking Caulk is used to seal gaps and seems between intersecting surfaces (baseboards|walls, trim|walls, &amp;hellip;). Thus, caulking not only helps to insulate your buildings, but is also an important aesthetic process.
Flashing Light interacting differently with different parts of the same surface creates a discrepancy in it&amp;rsquo;s visual experience. Depending on the amount and direction of the light, flashing can be very [noticible](https://www.google.ca/?gws_rd=ssl#q=paint flashing&amp;amp;tbm=isch).</description></item><item><title>Spraying</title><link>https://cottagepainter.github.io/resources/spraying/</link><pubDate>Sat, 20 Apr 2019 11:40:14 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://cottagepainter.github.io/resources/spraying/</guid><description>Spraying is a basic method of paint-application for the modern painter, forming a trinity with the traditional methods of brushing and rolling.
The main benefit of spraying is speed. A two-story house that used to take 10 days to paint with a brush and roller, can be sprayed in 1 or 2 days by just one person. An incredible productivity boost!
Spraying also leaves the finest finish. Anytime paint is applied with a brush, lap marks, caused by the bristles dragging out the paint, are inevitably left behind and visible to the critical eye.</description></item><item><title>Equipment</title><link>https://cottagepainter.github.io/resources/equipment/</link><pubDate>Sat, 20 Apr 2019 11:40:08 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://cottagepainter.github.io/resources/equipment/</guid><description>Caulking Ladders Masking Spackling Spraying Washing Caulking After a couple years of testing, I&amp;rsquo;ve decided that Big Stretch is the only caulk worth using. Although it is expensive (~$6.00 a tube), it works where the others failed. This is especially true on the Bay, where buildings are normally old, wooden, and very exposed.
Ladders 24-ft Werner Aluminum Extension Ladder 8-ft Werner Fiberglass Stepladder.</description></item><item><title>What is Paint?</title><link>https://cottagepainter.github.io/resources/paint/</link><pubDate>Sat, 20 Apr 2019 11:39:48 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://cottagepainter.github.io/resources/paint/</guid><description>The term paint has become convoluted due to the terminology used by &amp;lsquo;paint&amp;rsquo;-manufactures in their marketing. People use the word &amp;lsquo;paint&amp;rsquo; for anything that you can put on with a brush, hence the verb &amp;lsquo;to paint&amp;rsquo;. The problem is that the &amp;lsquo;paint&amp;rsquo;-industry uses the word &amp;lsquo;paint&amp;rsquo; for a class of its products. It&amp;rsquo;s like a restaurant replacing the word &amp;lsquo;entree&amp;rsquo; with &amp;lsquo;food&amp;rsquo;. As a consequence, people end up calling different things &amp;lsquo;paint&amp;rsquo;, even thou they might differ greatly in function.</description></item><item><title>Exterior Painting</title><link>https://cottagepainter.github.io/services/exterior-painting/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2019 15:07:34 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://cottagepainter.github.io/services/exterior-painting/</guid><description>I offer modern, efficient, correct, large-scale exterior painting. Modern; I use the most modern equipment and tools as the basis of my process. Efficient; my process is effective and practiced. Correct; my process is warranty-valid according to the paint manufacturer. Large-scale; my process can handle any size job on the Bay.
Process Estimation Washing Preparation Application Cleanup Estimation All services I provide are offered with a firm, quoted, transparent price.</description></item><item><title>Gutter Cleaning</title><link>https://cottagepainter.github.io/services/gutter-cleaning/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2019 15:07:34 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://cottagepainter.github.io/services/gutter-cleaning/</guid><description>Using a high-pressure pressure washer, an extension wand, and a special attachment, I am able to wash-out your eavestroughs without ever having to climb a ladder. Fast, efficient, and highly effective.
This service is offered at a discounted price to anyone that hires me for exterior painting, since it can be done at the same time as the washing.</description></item><item><title>Interior Painting</title><link>https://cottagepainter.github.io/services/interior-painting/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2019 15:07:34 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://cottagepainter.github.io/services/interior-painting/</guid><description>I offer modern, efficient, correct, small-scale interior painting. Modern; I use the most modern equipment and tools as the basis of my process. Efficient; my process is effective and practiced. Correct; my process is warranty-valid according to the paint manufacturer. Small-scale; my process can handle small jobs (trim-repaints, bedrooms, &amp;hellip;).
The Process Estimation Washing Preparation Application Cleanup Estimation All services I provide are offered with a firm, quoted, transparent price.</description></item><item><title>About Myself</title><link>https://cottagepainter.github.io/about/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cottagepainter.github.io/about/</guid><description>My name is Currie Carmichael, I&amp;rsquo;m a professional painter who&amp;rsquo;s been serving the SSCA for the past 4 years. I specialize in exterior-repaints of wood and composite-sided houses and buildings. I have been a cottager in the area my entire life and am prepared, equipped, and ready to handle any project on the Bay.
My season generally lasts from mid-May until September. I primarily focus on exterior-work during this time. Although this is the case, I am more then capable of handling your interior projects.</description></item><item><title>Contact</title><link>https://cottagepainter.github.io/contact/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cottagepainter.github.io/contact/</guid><description/></item><item><title>References</title><link>https://cottagepainter.github.io/references/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cottagepainter.github.io/references/</guid><description>Client Island Description Alex Scott
Iron City
Complete exterior trim repaint (2019)
Bert &amp;amp; Sarah Liverance
Wahsoune
Exterior repaint of south wall on the main cottage (2016)
Carolyn Patterson
Hideaway
Exterior repaint of a sleeping cabin (2016)
Interior repaint of same sleeping cabin (2017)</description></item></channel></rss>