<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Services on Cottage Painter</title>
    <link>https://cottagepainter.github.io/services/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Services on Cottage Painter</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2019 15:07:34 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://cottagepainter.github.io/services/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Exterior Painting</title>
      <link>https://cottagepainter.github.io/services/exterior-painting/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2019 15:07:34 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cottagepainter.github.io/services/exterior-painting/</guid>
      <description>I offer modern, efficient, correct, large-scale exterior painting. Modern; I use the most modern equipment and tools as the basis of my process. Efficient; my process is effective and practiced. Correct; my process is warranty-valid according to the paint manufacturer. Large-scale; my process can handle any size job on the Bay.
Process     Estimation Washing Preparation Application Cleanup  Estimation    All services I provide are offered with a firm, quoted, transparent price.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gutter Cleaning</title>
      <link>https://cottagepainter.github.io/services/gutter-cleaning/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2019 15:07:34 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cottagepainter.github.io/services/gutter-cleaning/</guid>
      <description>Using a high-pressure pressure washer, an extension wand, and a special attachment, I am able to wash-out your eavestroughs without ever having to climb a ladder. Fast, efficient, and highly effective.
This service is offered at a discounted price to anyone that hires me for exterior painting, since it can be done at the same time as the washing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Interior Painting</title>
      <link>https://cottagepainter.github.io/services/interior-painting/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2019 15:07:34 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cottagepainter.github.io/services/interior-painting/</guid>
      <description>I offer modern, efficient, correct, small-scale interior painting. Modern; I use the most modern equipment and tools as the basis of my process. Efficient; my process is effective and practiced. Correct; my process is warranty-valid according to the paint manufacturer. Small-scale; my process can handle small jobs (trim-repaints, bedrooms, &amp;hellip;).
The Process     Estimation Washing Preparation Application Cleanup  Estimation    All services I provide are offered with a firm, quoted, transparent price.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>